{
  "LevelId": 33,
  "Questions": [
    {
      "id": 336,
      "level_image": 6,
      "answer_text": "BACKBITER",
      "question": "often spreading harmful gossip or criticism"
    },
    {
      "id": 337,
      "level_image": 6,
      "answer_text": "JACKKNIFE",
      "question": "refer to a folding knife with blades that pivot at the end,"
    },
    {
      "id": 338,
      "level_image": 6,
      "answer_text": "LEGENDARY",
      "question": "describe something or someone with extraordinary fame, excellence,"
    },
    {
      "id": 339,
      "level_image": 6,
      "answer_text": "KICKBOXER",
      "question": "athlete trained in a hybrid martial art"
    },
    {
      "id": 340,
      "level_image": 6,
      "answer_text": "AIRLINERS",
      "question": "long-range aircraft is designed for transporting passengers"
    },
    {
      "id": 341,
      "level_image": 6,
      "answer_text": "GRANDEZZA",
      "question": "Italian word, meaning \"grandeur\" or \"greatness,\" is often used to describe"
    },
    {
      "id": 342,
      "level_image": 6,
      "answer_text": "BABYISHLY",
      "question": "manner might someone behave if they are acting in an overly childish or infantile way"
    },
    {
      "id": 343,
      "level_image": 6,
      "answer_text": "APPETIZER",
      "question": "flavorful dish served before the main course to stimulate one's appetite"
    },
    {
      "id": 344,
      "level_image": 6,
      "answer_text": "FLIMMAKER",
      "question": "professional involved in the creation and production of films,"
    },
    {
      "id": 345,
      "level_image": 0,
      "answer_text": "INDONESIA",
      "question": "Southeast Asian country is the world's largest archipelago,"
    }
  ]
}